♪♪♪
What are you doing today?
I'm free.
Is he still not here?
Still not here?
I'm so excited about today.
Wait, I miss this place!
We used to go here for the choir competition.
Good morning.
Wow.
What's with all the pieces?
Oh, no.
It's definitely not easy.
It's so much better.
It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo.
Erm, it's a bit mushy.
Some people might be expecting a Yankee.
A competition for everyone!
Well, Mire-chan and I had this together.
The home screen of my phone is a live drawing of Mire-chan.
Seeno.
This is Maimi Sakuragi. Please.
I'm a little nervous because I have a lot of relatives coming over today.
Isn't this place Mito?
Is Mito better?
Ibaraki.
Where is this place?
Ibaraki!
We are Ebichu!
One song!
Ute!
Ebichu!
Fight!
Yuna.
Lift your feet.
Lift your legs. Ready.
Watch where you're going.
It's that way.
What do you think? Cocona Battle.
I'm really into it.
Here.
I understand. I understand.
Cocona's voice coming out of the earpiece is really loud.
It's true.
She says she's really good.
She's good.
She was good.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
Subscribe to our channel!